(Penny:)It's open.
(Leonard:)Hey, you ready to go?
Yeah, ju...
Hang on, let me just finish this chapter.
- Well, can you finish it later?
- No, I can't.
(Penny:)Reading books is a big part
of my life now because, you know:
"We'd have more fun things to talk about
if I read more."
(Leonard:)Great. Good, great.
What are you reading?
Two Weeks to Rock-Hard Abs.
(Leonard:)They kind of spoil the ending
right in the name of that, don't they?
(Leonard:)All right. Look.
Just remember how this works.
(Leonard:)We don't get mad about these things.
Speaking of which, l've addressed
your bug report on my date planning.
I've got a really fun evening for you.
It's kind of a surprise.
All right, terrific. Let me just go
find a pair of shoes that aren't so tall.
(Penny:)We wouldn't want you to feel like you
were "out for a walk with your mommy."